When I got home with it he was in much worse condition
than I thought, even though it was inspected two days
before I bought it.
The last inspection in life for exactly 50.
So when I got home with it so I discovered
That two shock absorbers were stuck with just one bolt.
The other end hung completely loose and all four feathers were so exhausted
So they hung on the rubber impact.
Bad repairs a little everywhere holes in the exhaust system.
How it went through the inspection, I do not understand that at all.
Much like the inspection was ten meters away from
It wasn't very rust on it.
However, the repairs were a bit like that you can say.
But roasting is, they are beautiful in some way.
After all, the rear screens are epic.
Hahaha!.
Someone has stood with a sledgehammer and walked on there
And then they have thrown over the features with putty spade with such stripes in as well as
And drawn so you see the marks after the brush strokes on the front screen.
Yes, it is beautiful.
It will be interesting.
He was probably a brick and not a car plate maker.
The one who was on this one.
Yes, that's about this.
But the waffle, stop blowing, it blows in all directions now all of a sudden.
So there are throwing winds sometimes.
Hell how fast it dries.
The sun is shining on us and it pulls right away.
Now I run some half -paint this gray too.
Love that the cracks come out when I do.
Bird shit on the roof where it should remain.
What did you say?
The three spots with bird shit on the roof are the ones left.
We can remove them if you want, but it is optional.
But it was fortunate that they did not drill into the tank
or something.
It is usually quite long screws too, kind of one
and a half to two centimeters.
You can screw through a lot when you are doing it,
But they have actually succeeded in the rear window because they have not cracked the boxes.
It's a little cheating I think.
But now I have soon covered so all the old is gone.
I'll fix the front and rear end too so it's over, painted and clear.
Then I can start driving.
With the design I will run a bit with tape and stuff and put up lines and stuff.